<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Speed Loan Coach</string>

    <string name="app_title">
        <font color="#3783FB">F</font><font color="#000000">ast </font>
      <font color="#3783FB">L</font><font color="#000000">oan </font>
        <font color="#3783FB">C</font><font color="#000000">oach</font>
    </string>
    <string name="special_case">User-Generated Content Policy(UGC) By pressing the <b>&#34;Accept&#34;</b> button, I declare I have read and accepted the following condition of use:</string>
    <string name="autoloandata">1. Check your credit To get a car loan, your first step should be to check your credit report and credit score. Your credit score is a number on a scale ranging from 300 to 850 that looks at your borrowing history to tell lenders how likely you are to repay what you borrow. It can be found for free through sites like Credit Karma. Your credit score will have a big impact on the amount you will pay to borrow, or the interest rate of your loan. There is no official minimum credit score needed to buy a car, but the best interest rates go to borrowers with credit scores above 660. Knowing your credit score up front can help you tailor your lender search to your specific situation, and avoid any surprises as you start shopping.2. Determine how much you need to borrow, and what you can afford This far in the process, you should already know what type of car you are aiming to buy. Now is the time to get more specific. You will want to consider: The monthly payment. How much can you afford to pay each month? How much you can put down. The rule of thumb is a 20% down payment on a car. The more money you can put down up front, the smaller the monthly payment will be. How long a loan you will need. Longer loans may reduce the amount you owe each month, but they could cause you to be upside down on your loan, a situation where the amount due on your loan is greater than the car is value. Cars are notorious for depreciation, or losing significant value over time. Choose a loan that is 60 months or shorter to avoid an upside-down loan. If your loan is too long, consider choosing a less expensive car, making a larger down payment, or paying more each month. 3. Choose a few lenders you would like to work with Once you know how much you can afford and your credit score, start looking for a lender. A few options include: Credit unions. These local institutions often offer low interest rates than large banks. You will have to become a member, and membership is usually bound to things like geographic location or an employer. Banks. Most banks also give loans like auto loans. Banks you already have a relationship with may offer you affordable rates, and that may be worth a look. However, many larger banks auto loans generally start with a higher interest rate than credit unions. Online lenders. A number of online-only banks and lenders offer car loans. While they can sometimes offer lower rates due to the fact that they donot have any overhead costs, there is no brick-and-mortar office to visit if that is important to you. 4. Get pre-approved through those lenders Once you have picked a few lenders, start applying for pre-approvals. A pre-approval is a bank is way of conditionally saying that they are willing to lend to you. You can get pre-approved by as many lenders as you would like - you will want to check with a few lenders to compare the interest rates they offer. Dealerships can also help you arrange financing, but it is worth shopping around beforehand. It is common practice for dealerships to mark up financing rates, so shopping around could help you be sure that the dealership is offer is the best deal. 5. Compare your pre-approval offers Once you start getting pre-approvals, you will have two weeks to gather as many as you would like without having multiple hard credit inquiries appear on your credit report - they will all appear as one. Pre-approvals are generally good for 30 or 60 days, depending on the lender. Compare your pre-approval offers to find the offer that best fits your monthly budget, carries the lowest APR or interest rate, and has the shortest term. 6. Accept an offer Now is the time to accept the loan offer that you are happy with. Make sure you have the proper documentation on hand, like your driver is license, proof of income, proof of insurance, and proof of residency, depending on the lender. You will also want to bring the pre-approval paperwork and your checkbook if you are making a down payment. The bank will then arrange for the funds or a blank check to be sent to you or the dealership, and you are ready to buy the car. 7. Head to the dealership This is the fun part: Pick out the car. Then, you will sign some paperwork at the dealership. Oftentimes, the lender you choose will send you a blank check, and you will fill it out once you and the dealer have settled on a price. You will make your down payment at this point, too. After you have left the lot, the lender will send you information on how much you owe and how to pay. 8. Make (and potentially automate) your payments Many lenders offer a small interest rate discount when you sign up for an automatic payment - it makes your car payment one less thing to think about, and could takes a bit off the interest you owe. When you set up automatic payments, funds will be automatically deducted from your bank accounts on a monthly date you choose. Autopay can be set up through your lender online or over the phone. Many lenders will let you know about rate discounts before and as you apply on their websites, or through the paperwork sent to you after finalizing your loan.</string>
    <string name="bussinessloandata">Here’s a step-wise guide about how to get a loan for business: 1) Identify the different loan types It is good to know what type of business loans are available and their terms and conditions. Based on the business size and specific requirements, applicants can choose from a variety of MSME and SME loans or working capital loans. It can even be a machinery loan if the business owner’s primary goal is to purchase equipment for expansion. While term loans are best for large-scale business expansion, a line of credit may be ideal for meeting daily operational costs. Borrowers can start off with microloans for smaller cash requirements. Those with bad credit or no credit history may have to look for secured loans that require collateral. 2) Choose the lender and the application medium Once applicants have a clear idea about the type of loan that best suits them, decide the lender. In India, there are several business loan providers. A critical analysis of a lender’s loan terms and eligibility criteria can be of great help. Loan approval takes time. But those needing quick money can choose to go online. Others who are not comfortable online, can choose to visit the lender’s branch with the required documents and a duly signed application form. 3) Check credit score Lenders prefer applicants with a good credit history and a credit score above 700. A negative credit history reflecting late or missed payments can be a warning for lenders. Those with a poor credit score can think of alternative lending solutions and also focus on rebuilding them. 4) Loan application form Applicants must treat every step of the loan application with the utmost care. Since lenders cross-verify every small information about the applicant, it is sensible to be true and precise about every detail. 5) Prepare a business plan The applicant must submit a detailed business plan along with the loan application. The business plan should clearly state the firm’s purpose, past business track records and future ambitions. It should also specify the purpose of the loan. In other words, the borrowers must tell the lender what the loan is for and how they plan to use the money. 6) Preparing essential documents Borrowers must keep the necessary documents ready. Certain documents like the company’s bank statements for the last six months, KYC documents of the company (PAN card, ownership papers), KYC documents of the business owner (CIBIL score, PAN number) and financial statements like income tax returns for the last two years, audited balance sheet for the previous two years are necessary to get a business loan application approved. All these documents must be self-attested and up-to-date. It must be remembered that any incorrect information can cause unnecessary delays in loan disbursement. Nowadays, many lenders provide online services for document verification. Applicants applying on the bank’s website just need to upload the documents in a specific format and wait for the lenders’ approval. 7) Evaluate the EMI Before filling out a loan application form, applicants must always calculate the exact financial requirements of the firm. An amount more than what is required can add to more debt. Likewise, inadequate funds can cause bottlenecks. Another important factor to consider is to evaluate one’s repayment capacity. During the loan tenor, the borrower repays the principal amount borrowed from the bank as well as the interest that accumulates on that principal. Most lenders today provide a free online business loan EMI calculator to estimate the monthly repayment amount. After weighing all the pros and cons of loans, applicants can submit the application and apply for a loan for business. The lender reviews the application and does a background check before making the loan offer. If the borrower agrees to the terms and conditions of the loan, it will be closed and disbursed.</string>
    <string name="homeloandata">Step by step – Home Loan Procedure Step 1: Filling the form Home Loan Procedure starts with filling out the loan application form. Applying for a Home Loan from HDFC Bank is easy. Following are the basic details which you will have to fill in the form: Name Address Contact details – phone number and email ID Education Type of employment – salaried or self-employed Income earned Step 2: Documentation Once you fill in your basic details, you will have to attach the following documents for verification: Identity proof – PAN card/ Aadhar Card / Voter ID/ Driving license Address of proof – can be a copy of any utility bill Salary slips of the last 3 months Proof of employment Bank statements of the last 6 months Form 16 Note: If you are a self-employed individual, you need to provide the ITR of the last 2 years and the other income documents. Step 3: Processing and Verification On submission of the form along with the required documents, the bank starts processing your Home Loan application. The bank will verify all the documents provided by you. A bank representative may even visit your workplace or home for the same. The next step is checking your creditworthiness as a borrower. The bank conducts an extensive enquiry into your credit score. Hence it is important that you maintain a healthy credit history. If all your documents are in order and you have a satisfactory credit score and report, the bank will proceed with your loan application. Step 4: Sanction Letter On successful approval of your Home Loan application, the bank will send you a sanction letter. This letter acts as proof that the bank has approved your loan. All essential details about the loan transaction are enclosed in this letter, such as: The loan amount you are eligible for. The interest rate offered. Whether the interest rate is fixed or variable. Tenure of repayment. Terms and conditions of repayment. Read more about fixed or floating interest rates for Home Loans here. After carefully reviewing all the points mentioned in the sanction letter, you can sign the letter and send it back to the bank. Only after the bank receives the signed letter from you, the Home Loan procedure moves to the next step. Step 5: Secure Payment Fee On signing the sanction letter, you will have to pay a one-time secure payment fee. The bank may ask you to pay the fee upfront either before or after the loan sanction. Step 6: Legal and Technical Check Before the bank disburses the loan amount, it conducts legal and technical checks. The bank representatives will verify the property you have applied the loan for. They will check if the ownership rights of the property are transparent. The representatives will also check if the documents submitted, and the proofs provided have any conflicting information. During the technical check, the bank representatives will evaluate the actual value of the property. The status of the property – under construction or resale – will also be taken into consideration. If the property is under construction, they will check the construction stage and quality of the work. Whereas, if the property is a resale one, the bank will check the age and maintenance of the property. In case of the resale, the bank may also check if the property has already been mortgaged before. Step 7: Loan Disbursal Once the bank is satisfied with the checks conducted, your Home Loan application will be approved. You will receive a final agreement letter. Post loan disbursal, you will receive a welcome kit and a detailed housing loan EMI schedule. It is important that you check whether you meet the required Home Loan eligibility criteria before applying for the loan. You can seek professional guidance here to make a more informed decision. If you already are a borrower and want to switch your lender, you can opt for the Home Loan Transfer procedure.</string>
    <string name="moratagesdata">There are broadly eight steps to the loan application process: 1. Fill up the home loan Application Form: Every would-be borrower, like Dinesh, has to fill up a home loan application form. This will involve information like name, address, income details and proof, employment details, education details, and phone number. Dinesh will also have to furnish proofs for all the above as well as salary slips-for the latest 3 months, employment proof, bank statements – for the latest 6 months and the latest Form 16, since he is a salaried employee. Self-employed borrowers will have to provide the full set of ITR returns for the last two years along with other income documents. 2. Pay the Processing Fee: After Dinesh submits his documents he has to pay the initial processing fee as decided by the bank, which is non-refundable. This is charged for the preliminary work the bank does to verify borrower details and to investigate the property’s value and ownership title. The remaining processing fee is taken later on at the time of disbursement. But Dinesh’s loan will not be approved just because he has paid these fees. The fees vary from bank to bank. It may be either a fixed amount or a percentage of the loan amount. Axis Bank, for example, charges a fee up to 1% of the loan amount (with a minimum of Rs. 10,000+ applicable taxes). 3. Bank Discussion: The bank usually takes a decision as per bank credit policy on whether to approve or reject the loan application within 5 working days. The bank may call Dinesh for a telephonic discussion. This is the case for most salaried employees. In case of self-employed borrowers, the bank’s representative may visit the customer’s place of work for personal discussion and to understand about their business. This will help the credit underwriter to upraise loan in a better way. [Also Read: Home Loan Balance Transfer - All You Need To Know] 4. Document Verification: Once the bank completes the personal discussion with Dinesh, it will start calculating his eligibility. This could involve a bank official visiting his current residence and/or getting in touch with his employers. The bank will check Dinesh is credit score with a bureau like CIBIL. 5. Approval Process: This is the process (as per Bank Credit Policy) that will decide if the bank will approve Dinesh’s loan application. Dinesh has to make sure that all his documents are in order; otherwise, his application may get rejected. 6. Sanction Letter: The bank will send Dinesh a loan sanction letter if his loan is approved. This letter will contain Dinesh’s eligible loan amount, interest rate and type (fixed or variable) applicable, loan tenure with terms &amp; condition. If Dinesh accepts it, he has to sign it and send a copy to the bank. 7. Property Verification: Now that the loan has been approved and accepted, the bank will verify the property. It will do a legal check on the property to ensure the title is clear and there is no dispute or conflict regarding the same. It will also conduct a technical valuation on the property. If the property is under construction, it will check the stage, progress and quality of construction as well. If the property is a resale property, the bank will check the age, quality and maintenance levels of the building. It will also check if the property is already mortgaged. Dinesh will have to submit all property papers, including original copies of the title deed, to the bank. These papers are mortgaged with the bank until Dinesh repays the loan in full. 8. Loan Disbursal: Once the property verification is complete, the customer has to provide all documents as per legal and technical reports. Following this loan agreement is signed and if all documents are in order, the loan will get disbursed and the cheque will be handed over to the customer. The cheque may be made in favour of the builder, if you are purchasing the property from a builder. Post-disbursement, the bank will send the customer the welcome kit, along with the repayment schedule. The EMI payment is done either through Standing Instructions, if the account from which payment is being made is from the same bank, or through NACH mandate - if the account from which payment is being made is with another bank. (NACH or Nationalised Automated Clearing House Payment Solution is the centralised system that facilitates the seamless transactions between banks).</string>
    <string name="paydayloandata">In order to apply for a payday loan, follow these steps: When applying for payday loans, you must be aware of certain policies, such as loan renewal policies, rollover rules, and early repayment penalties. In order to apply for a payday loan, follow these steps: Step 1 - Fill out your personal information When entering your personal information, make sure that you use the correct name, address, phone number, date of birth and social security number. This will ensure that lenders can easily verify your identity during the approval process. Step 2 - Provide proof of income You will need to provide proof that you are employed or have some other source of income. This can be your most recent pay stub, on-demand employment earnings, unemployment benefits statement, pension award letter or Social Security disability award letter. Step 3 - Fill out your bank account details Payday lenders require that you provide them with your bank account details so they can easily deposit the funds as soon as possible. Most payday loan lenders usually deposit the funds on the next business day following the approval; however, some lenders may take up to two days to process your application and deposit your funds. Step 4 - Agree to the fees and terms Once you have completed your application, review all of the fees and terms. If everything is correct, proceed to click submit or next to complete your application. This will send it directly to a lender for review. You should receive an instant response from a lender about whether you have been approved for the loan. How to choose a payday loan lender? If you are thinking of applying for payday loans, then it is important that you search only through reputed lending companies that offer fair interest rates and transparent terms and conditions. Here are some tips on how to choose a reputable payday lender: 1. A reputable payday lender must not charge any upfront fees. 2. A reputable payday lender will not engage in any sort of coercion or harassment if you reject their offer to provide you with a loan. 3. A reputable payday lender should be able to lend you money even if your credit score is low. 4. A reputable payday lender will never charge hidden fees. 5. Look for customer testimonials online to see what other customers are saying about the companies service, pricing and convenience.</string>
    <string name="personaldata">A Personal Loan has flexible repayment terms and usually no security or collateral is required. Here is a five-step guide on how to get a Personal Loan. From documents required to how to apply for a Personal Loan, we have all the angles covered: Step 1: Determine your requirement Figure out why you need a Personal Loan and how much you need. For example, you may need a loan to fund your wedding or to renovate your home. And you may need just Rs. 1 lac or Rs. 10 lac. Step 2: Check loan eligibility Once you know how much you need, you should check whether you are eligible. You can visit the HDFC Bank Personal Loan Eligibility Calculator online, to find out how much you can borrow as Personal Loan. HDFC Bank offers loans up to Rs. 40 lac. Read more about how to calculate your Personal Loan EMI and how to lower it. Step 3: Calculate monthly instalments Use an online EMI tool to calculate your approximate loan repayments every month. You can modify the interest rate and tenure to match your monthly income, like on HDFC Bank Personal Loan EMI calculator. HDFC Bank offers pocket friendly EMIs on all its Personal Loan starting at Rs. 1878 per lac * (T&amp;C). Step 4: Approach the bank You can apply for a Personal Loan with HDFC Bank in a variety of ways: Via NetBanking, online on the HDFC Bank website, at an ATM or by visiting a branch. Step 5: Submit documents Next find out what documents are required for a Personal Loan. Usually, you will need income proof (bank statements, salary slips or IT returns), address proof and ID proof. Hand over copies of your Personal Loan documents at the bank. Wait for funds to be remitted to your account. HDFC Bank disburses funds for pre-approved loans to customers in 10 seconds*, and for non-HDFC Bank customers in 4 hours*.</string>
    <string name="smallbusinessdata">If you determine that it’s best to go the small business loan application route, learn how to apply for a small business loan using these seven steps. 1. Determine how much you need First things first, determine how much of a loan you need by listing out what you need the funds for. You may need a small business loan to: Start your business Expand Purchase equipment Increase inventory Improve cash flow What you need the funds for can vary depending on what stage of “life” your business is in (e.g., startup). To determine the ideal loan amount for your business, make a list of what you plan on using the funds for. Then, do a little research to help guesstimate how much in loans you’ll need to cover the costs. 2. Review your credit score and history Part of the loan process includes lenders looking at your credit history and score. And in many cases, lenders may look at both personal and business credit information. It’s a good rule of thumb to look at where your credit stands before you start applying for any type of loan—especially if you’re a newer business owner. Before applying for a small business loan, check out your credit history and score. You can request a credit score from an agency (e.g., Dun &amp; Bradstreet). Or, you may be able to get a good idea of where your credit stands from reports from your bank and credit card companies. Review your credit reports after you gather them. And, check out your credit score. A personal score of 700 or more is generally considered good (300 – 850 range). However, many lenders will want to see a minimum score of 680. A good business credit score is typically 75 or above (0 – 100 range). The higher your credit score and the better your credit history, the more likely you are to receive a loan. 3. Review your loan options There are a variety of loan options to choose from nowadays. Before you start shopping around for a lender and applying for a loan, you need to know the different types. Many loans are designed for certain types of businesses or specific financial situations. Here are a few types of business loans to look into: 4. Check out your local SCORE and SBDC offices If you’re a newer business, you may want to consider checking out your local SCORE and SBDC offices. Small Business Development Center (SBDC) and SCORE provide confidential advice to small businesses across the country. SCORE consists of a retired group of business executives who can provide one-on-one guidance to business owners. SBDC, part of the Small Business Administration, also exists to help small businesses. Both organizations can help assist you with the business loan application process and answer any questions you may have. 5. Determine which type of lender is the best fit for you When it comes to getting a small business loan, you have a number of options. You’re not tied down to only getting a loan from a large, national bank. You can also receive a loan from a smaller lender. Here are a few types of lenders you can choose from: Banks Credit unions Nonprofit lenders Online lenders Microlenders The lender you may go with can vary depending on the type of loan you want (think back to Step #3). Before choosing a lender, do your research. Look at factors like interest rates and total borrowing costs. And, be sure to look at reviews to see what other clients have to say. 6. Gather necessary documents After you narrow down which lender you want to go with, find out what documentation the lender requires for a loan. Generally, you may need to provide the following information: Business plan Financial statements Business banking account Bank statements Business license and permits Identification (e.g., driver’s license) Other business documents (e.g., articles of incorporation) Business tax returns If you’re a new business, you may not have all of the above information yet. Before you apply for a loan, make sure you find out what information you need and what accounts you must set up. Each lender has its own requirements and eligibility criteria. So, check with your potential lender to find out what specific information you need to gather. 7. Complete your application Gather all of your necessary documents? Great! Now comes the fun part: Submitting your application and officially applying for the loan. Book an appointment with a lender to get the ball rolling on your business loan application. Depending on your lender, you may be able to apply online or over the phone. However, many lenders require you to fill out a paper application in person. Whatever method your lender allows, make sure you have your documents handy (e.g., business licenses and permits, ID, etc.). Once you complete your application, it will go through an underwriting process with the lender. An underwriting process verifies your information (e.g., income, debt, credit, etc.) to issue an approval for the loan. The application, underwriting, and funding process may take anywhere from a few days to a few months. Check with your lender to get an estimate of how long the process will take before you can receive a loan. In some cases, you may need to make a pitch to your loan officer or lender on why they should trust your business with the loan money. This is where your business plan can come into play. To ensure you’re prepared, rehearse and plan your talking points.</string>
    <string name="strNoInternet">No internet connection.</string>
    <string name="studentloandata">The cost of seeking a quality education is rising every day. Schools and universities charge fees to the tune of several lakhs of rupees, making it impossible for parents to fully fund their child’s education. High costs of education are especially a burden on parents whose children aspire to attend private institutions in India or prestigious universities abroad. In such a situation, the only respite is offered by banks which provide education loans. Such loans cover everything, from tuition fees and cost of books, apparatus etc., to lodging charges, dormitory fees, travel allowance and so on. Let us find out the step-by-step procedure to take education loan. Step 1 – Filling the application form Just like with any other loan, the first step is to fill an application form. The application form is a simple form in which you must provide your personal contact details as well as your academic details. Ensure that you provide accurate and truthful information in this form. As per the instructions of the Department of Financial Services, Ministry of Finance, Government of India, all education loan applications (including applications received by Bank in physical format) are to be applied through Vidya Lakshmi portal, i.e. https://www.vidyalakshmi.co.in/Students Step 2 – Interview The next step in the education loan procedure is the interview round. After considering your application, your bank typically calls you for a personal discussion or an interview. Note that the loan is offered to the student and co-obligation of parents/ guardian and the student is considered as the main loan applicant. You may be asked several questions pertaining to your academic performance, the institute you wish to attend, the course selected by you, future scope of your chosen course and so on. You must be honest and should be able to convince the bank that you are choosing a stream that has the potential to generate good income, thus enabling you to repay the loan. Step 3 – Documentation Before the loan is processed you need to prove to the bank that your chosen university has extended an offer of admission. This is the primary document that all banks ask for, even before one begins the actual loan application process. The bank can get in touch with the university to verify your enrolment. If your education loan amount exceeds ₹4,00,000, you would be required to provide some sort of collateral in the form of third party Guarantee if the required loan amount is upto Rs.7,50,000, and if it exceeds 7,50,000 you are required to provide collateral security equivalent to 100 % of the loan amount along with assignment of future income of the student for payment of instalments. Assignment of future income of the student for payment of instalments is applicable to all Education Loans irrespective of Loan amount. Step 4 – Loan approval As per the education loan repayment procedure, banks offer the loan to the student applicant, and since the student cannot repay the loan until the course is completed, the bank considers parents/guardians as co-borrower of the loan. the bank also verifies the credit history of the co-borrower/guarantor before sanctioning the loan. bank offers moratorium period equivalent to the course period plus year and it is optional for the borrowers to serve the interest education loan during this moratorium period. the loan is approved, the borrowers will receive a sanction letter from the bank. the borrowers accept the terms and conditions of sanction, bank calls them for execution of loan documents and hand over of collateral security papers in original to the bank if it is required as per terms of Step 5 – Loan disbursal The final step in the education bank loan procedure is loan disbursal. Banks typically directly disburse the loan to your chosen university by way of Banker’s cheque, Demand draft or SWIFT message as per the location of the chosen University/Institution along with your margin if stipulated in Sanction.</string>

    <string name="loan_type">
     <font color="#3783FB">L</font><font color="#000000">oan </font>
    <font color="#3783FB">T</font><font color="#000000">ype </font>
    </string>
    <string name="loan_status">
      <font color="#3783FB">L</font><font color="#000000">oan </font>
      <font color="#3783FB">S</font><font color="#000000">tatus </font>
    </string>
    <string name="personal_loan">
     <font color="#3783FB">P</font><font color="#000000">ersonal </font>
      <font color="#3783FB">L</font><font color="#000000">oan </font>
      <font color="#3783FB">I</font><font color="#000000">nformation </font>
    </string>
    <string name="personal">Personal Loan</string>
    <string name="loan_information">Loan Information</string>
    <string name="bank_balance">
        <font color="#3783FB">B</font><font color="#000000">ank </font>
      <font color="#3783FB">B</font><font color="#000000">alance </font>
    </string>
    <string name="loan_on_guide">
     <font color="#3783FB">S</font><font color="#000000">peed </font>
      <font color="#3783FB">L</font><font color="#000000">oan </font>
      <font color="#3783FB">C</font><font color="#000000">oach </font>
    </string>
    <string name="ifsc_micr_code">
    <font color="#3783FB">I</font><font color="#000000">FSC/ </font>
      <font color="#3783FB">M</font><font color="#000000">ICR </font>
      <font color="#3783FB">C</font><font color="#000000">ode </font>
    </string>
</resources>
